royalroadl.com 2018-11-16

# Privacy Policy of royalroadl.com

## Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  *     * ### Advertising

      * ### OpenX Ad Exchange, Google Ad Manager, Google AdSense, AppNexus and RhythmOne

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Analytics

      * ### Google Analytics and Analytics collected directly

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Commercial affiliation

      * ### Amazon Affiliation

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Contacting the User

      * ### Contact form

Personal Data: email address

    * ### Content commenting

      * ### Comment system managed directly

Personal Data: Cookies, email address, Usage Data and username

    * ### Handling payments

      * ### PayPal

Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Hosting and backend infrastructure

      * ### Microsoft Azure

Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

    * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

      * ### Twitter Tweet button and social widgets and Facebook Like button and social widgets

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Managing contacts and sending messages

      * ### Sendgrid

Personal Data: email address

    * ### Registration and authentication

      * ### Direct registration

Personal Data: date of birth, email address, gender, password, profile picture, username and website

    * ### SPAM protection

      * ### Google reCAPTCHA

Personal Data: Cookies and Usage Data

    * ### Traffic optimization and distribution

      * ### Cloudflare

Personal Data: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

## Further information about Personal Data

  *     * ### OneSignal

OneSignal is an SDK that allows communicating with the user via the messaging/notification tool. The data that OneSignal processes includes some or all of the following according to its privacy policy:

Your device's Advertising Identifier  
Your email address.  
Some or all of the following information: IP address, device push token, precise location, network information, language, timezone, product preferences, and privacy preferences.  
OneSignal also does the following "(...) we or a data partner we have engaged may collect and store a unique identifier matched to your mobile device, in order to deliver customized ads or content while you use applications or surf the internet, or to seek to identify you in a unique manner across other devices or browsers". For this, there is an opt-out possibility which you might think about implementing in your own privacy policy as well (copied below verbatim from the privacy policy by OneSignal:

End User Opt-Out  
End-users may opt-out of OneSignal related data collection by modifying the ad tracking settings on their device (identified by “Limit Ad Tracking” on iOS and “Opt out of interest-based ads” on Android), or by sending us a message through our contact form here https://onesignal.wufoo.com/forms/z16j8an40nfirat/.)

We have only implemented OneSignal for Premium users. 

    * ### Interest Based Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out  
<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/>

    * ### User-Generated content and activity

By using this service, you may engage in a lot of activities, including stating your personal information in your user biography, leaving comments, messages, reviews, forum posts, blog posts among other things. If you so choose to provide public information, you should be aware that this information can be read, and collected by other users of the service, and we are not responsible for any of the information you choose to submit. 

    * ### Customize the service

The data collected is used to customise the service for you, from providing a reading history list, to personalised content and recommendation. 

    * ### Regarding Data Retention

The data will only be retained in for as long as needed for the purposes it was collected or permitted by the applicable laws. We might keep specific data if there is a legal obligation to do so. 

    * ### Your rights concerning personal data:

You can download the data collected on the site about you using the following link:  
https://royalroadl.com/account/download

You can request for the deletion of your collected data by deleting your account:  
https://royalroadl.com/account/delete 

    * ### The Service is not directed to children under the age of 13

Users declare themselves to be adult according to their applicable legislation. Minors may use this Website only with the assistance of a parent or guardian. Under no circumstance persons under the age of 13 may use this Website.

    * ### Selling goods and services online

The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.  
The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by this Website depends on the payment system used.

  *     * ### Owner and Data Controller

6094/7  
Nazareth, Galilee 16040  
Israel

**Owner contact email:** admin@royalroadl.com
